VERONIKA GOLOVANOVA

WEB-DEVELOPER

E-MAIL: the veronika@rambler.ru RESIDENCE: CZECH REPUBLIC, PRAGUE

PHONE: +420775494689 CITIZENSHIP: RUSSIA, KRASNODAR

I am looking for the position of a frontend developer, because I'm interested in JS and I'm working on an active learning frameworks. Also I having a knowledge of PHP and Databases. I am a beginner web programmer but I already have experience in creating web pages for internal use in the company. Worked in Russia as a Firebird Database developer for about 3 years. At the moment I work as a programmer at a brigade in a Czech company.

SKILLS JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, PHP, MYSQL, FIREBIRDSQL, HTML, CSS, SASS, GULP, GITHUB,

SVN

AGE 26

LANGUAGES ENGLISH: INTERMEDIATE

CZECH: UPPER-INTERMEDIATE

RUSSIAN: PROFICIENCY

EDUCATION

KUBAN STATE UNIVERSITY

BACHELOR OF APPLIED INFORMATICS

- 2011-2015
- Russia, Krasnodar

VYSOKÁ ŠKOLA FINANČNÍ A SPRÁVNÍ

MASTER OF MARKETING COMMUNICATION

- 2018-2020 (Present)
- Czech Republic, Prague

WORK EXPERIENCE

SQL DEVELOPER

OOO "ITM" 1/2015 - 12/2017

RUSSIA, KRASNODAR

- Software development for a wholesale and retail company
- Database development Firebird SQL
- Software development for Portable Data Terminal on TSDserver and ZOPEserver (Python, JavaScript)

WEB DEVELOPER

DEVCOM, SPOL. S R.O. 3/2019 - PRESENT

CZECH REPUBLIC, PRAGUE

- Development of web pages for internal use
- Database development MySQL
- PHP (Import/Export files by Phpspreadsheet, connect to DB)
- Development of the interface part (JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, HTML)